dinnerthendessert.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy and Copyright - Dinner, then Dessert

* * *

This privacy policy sets out how Dinner, then Dessert uses and protects any information that you and your browser provide while using dinnerthendessert.com.

Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Advertising**

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website, including [AdThrive](http://www.adthrive.com/). These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data.  The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Dinner, then Dessert disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us.

—–

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice and was last updated on June 2, 2017. If you have any questions feel free to email me at contact@dinnerthendessert.com.

* * *

All posts will be made by me and all opinions contained in any page or post are mine unless explicitly stated otherwise.

I may receive payment or products from time to time to supplement my posts, but this will never influence what I write and I will disclose if I have received any such compensation to you, my dear readers.  I do this because I care about my readership and I want to be completely open and honest with you (oh, and also [I’m required by federal law](https://www.ftc.gov/news-events/press-releases/2009/10/ftc-publishes-final-guides-governing-endorsements-testimonials) to make those disclosures.)

I am more than happy to answer any questions about this if you e-mail me at contact@dinnerthendessert.com.

* * *

This website and its contents are the copyright of Dinner, then Dessert – © 2015-2016.  All rights reserved.

Dinner, then Dessert does not allow for its original recipes and pictures to be reproduced anywhere other than at this site unless authorization is given at the time of sharing (such as on sites like [foodgawker](http://foodgawker.com/post/archive/dinnerthendessert/)) and on social media platforms (like [Facebook ](https://www.facebook.com/DinnerthenDessert)and [Twitter](https://twitter.com/EatsnSweets)).

If you have an interest in posting one of my photos, text from my post or my recipes on another site, you must first contact me for and obtain permission.

If my recipe inspired you to make your own version, please reference my recipe and provide a link to it in your post. I would love for you to share if one of my recipes has inspired you, but if you do that I expect proper credit be sent back to me.  Some of my favorite recipes are inspired by other blogs, but I am always thorough in referencing them to show my love. Thanks for doing the same 🙂

If you need to reach me feel free to reach me for business purposes please use the following contact information:

Dinner, then Dessert Inc.  
2351 Sunset Blvd.  
Suite 170-950  
Rocklin, CA 95765  
(916) 625-6965
